Curriculum Vitae

SUMMARY

I had studied programming while in college, and decided to further develop my programming skills, especially in web programming. I have over 1 working years of experience as an Frontend Developer and passion for responsive website design and mobile-first design

INFORMATION

Full Name : Akhsan Bayu Riantama

Place, Date of Birth : Jayapura, 3 February 1999

Gender : Male

Address : Jl. Kopeng KM 5, Tegalrejo, Magelang

Email : akhsanby@gmail.com

Phone Number : +62895401224170

EDUCATION

team

STMIK Bina Patria, Kota Magelang - S.Kom

October 2017 - Desember 2021

Graduate as Informatics Engineering student with GPA 3.49 by produce a final assignment about step prediction with Al

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Digireg Indonesia - Frontend Developer March 2022 – February 2023
☐ Create a WebGIS frontend based on wireframes specified by the client or company
☐ Collaborate with Backend Developers in creating APIs to create response need of Frontend Developer
☐ Revise and create website-based company supporting tools according to company requests
Mitra Payment Indonesia - Technical Support
luly 2023 – December 2023
☐ Helping clients find solutions to payment gateway problems
☐ Educate new clients on how to use the company's payment gateway platform

Recording bugs on the payment gateway platform to be forwarded to the development

EXPERTISE AND SKILLS

Programing Language

PHP, Javascript

Framework / Library

Laravel, Codelgniter, VueJS, ReactJS

Design Tools

Inkscape, Figma

TRAINING & COURSE

Course Coding Online in Dicoding Academy

2020 - 2021

 Learn the basics of HTML and CSS as the pillars of a website. Learn the basics of JavaScript, from the fundamentals, syntax and features of ES6, to the concept of automation tests using popular frameworks.
Learn a lot & deeply about JavaScript to make website attractive.
Ecam a for a deepty about savadeript to make website attractive.
Course Coding Online in Udemy
2023 - Present
m currently studying Golang : Beginner to Advanced, Laravel : Beginner to Advanced, & NodeJS : Beginner to Advanced with Programmer Zaman Now
Kampus Merdeka with Hacktiv8
August 2021 – February 2022
☐ I learn basic HTML & Css in Kode.id
☐ I learn Javascript ES6 : Basic to Advance in Kode.id
☐ I lean Styling Component ReactJS in Kode.id
☐ I learn how to use ReactJS & React Native with reusable components & write clean code in Kode.id

SOCIAL MEDIA

Github - https://github.com/akhsanby

Portfolio web - https://akhsanby.vercel.app

Linkedin - https://www.linkedin.com/in/akhsanby